Hildebrand, George H. Papers /4040
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
George H. Hildebrand Papers
1954-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hildebrand, George H.
/4040
22 cubic feet
22 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
3079856
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 23, 2016
Biographical / Historical
George H. Hildebrand (July 7, 1913 May 18, 2007) was the Maxwell M. Upson Professor of Economics and Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University.
After graduating of the University of California-Berkeley (BA '35), Harvard University (MA '41), and Cornell University ('42), Hildebrand served in the military during World War II. From 1947 to 1954, he was a professor at the University of California-Los Angeles. In 1960, he became Professor of Economics and Industrial Relations at Cornell University, an in 1970 he became the Maxwell M. Upson Professor Economics and Industrial Relations.
Hildebrand was a member of the National Academy of Arbitrators, a member of panels of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Services and the New York State Public Employee Relations Board. He served as the Deputy Undersecretary of Labor of the U.S. Department of Labor (1969-1971), was elected President of the Industrial Relations Research Association (1971), and was founding director of Cornell's Center for the Study of American Political Economy (1980).
See the Cornell University Faculty Memorial Statement for Professor George H. Hildebrand: http://hdl.handle.net/1813/19045
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3008 AV: George H. Hildebrand "The Government's Wage-Price Policy: A Long Range View" Speech Audio-Visual Materials
Hildebrand, George Herbert.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3079856
- Beth Steel - Legal Background Documents, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bethlehem OFCC Case, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Bethlehem Steel - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bethlehem Steel -- Expenses, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Beth. Steel -- Company Actions Under Order, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Motions for Clarification - OFCC (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Beth. Steel - Motions of Parties--Memoranda, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Decision of the Secretary, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Interpretation-- Bethlehem Steel--Extension of AC Transfer Rights, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Request for Access to Information, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Interpretation--LDF, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Interpretation--Seniority and Transfer Information Committee, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Interpretation-- Eligibility for Promotion, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Interpretation- Qualifications Required of Transferring AC Employees, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Interpretation-- Transfers to White Units in Black Departments, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Interpretation-- Red Circle Rates, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Order Creating Coord. Comm. To Administer the Secretary's Decision (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Draft Letters to AC Employees, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Minutes-- Seniority and Transfer Information Committee -- Bethlehem Steel (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Q's and A's, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Promotions and Demotions under the Order, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 5/74 Consent Decree - Beth. Steel Corp., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Duplicate: OFCC Motions for Clarification, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Required Reports, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Book #1 Correspondence Bethlehem Steel Corporations, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Book #2 Correspondence Bethlehem Steel Corp., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- In the United States District Court for the Northern District of Alabama, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- The Migration of the Cotton Textile Industry from New England to the South: 1880 to 1930, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- The Politics of Wage-Price Decisions, A Four-Country Analysis, 1946-1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Annual Reports, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Grad. Exams, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Examinations, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Course Outlines, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Case Book ILAB Team Development and Reorganization Project, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Bureau of International Labor Affairs (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Oligopoly - Restricted Competition, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Eco. 885 - ILR 545.. Fall 1960 History of Economic Thought - Wage Theory (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Econ. 811 - Spring '62 Intermediate Eco. Theory, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Economics 876 Modern Economic History + its Critics, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Monopolistic Price Theory, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Eco. 511 - Lectures Fall 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Production Function - The Firm, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- ILR 241 - Room 217 MWF 10 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Case Functions - The Firm (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Reading Notes Vol. 4 - Business Cycle Theory, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- G. H. Hildebrand, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- The Theory of Markets and the Problem of Economic Crises, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Capital and Employment, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Reading Notes Vol. 3 - Business Cycle Theory, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Misc., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Formal Economic Theory, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Reading Notes Vol. 1 - Static Equilibrium Theory, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- John Bobs Clark, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Notes on Lectures in Price Theory, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Manual of Operations NLRB, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Mr. Hildebrand-Correspondence (Misc.) June 1969-Sept. 1971, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (J), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (K), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (I), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (H), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Mr. Hildebrand - Personal Cornell Federal Credit Union, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Personal - Mr. Hildebrand's Christmas Card List (1970) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Insurance) June, 1969 - Sept., 1971, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Mr. Hildebrand (Personal) HEW Research Grant Project No. CRD - 391-7, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Personal (Mrs. Marie Trump), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Mr. Hildebrand (Personal) Freedom House, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Mr. Hildebrand - Personal Photos and Biodata, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Mr. Hildebrand-Correspondence (Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (A), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Mr. Hildebrand -- Correspondence Prof. Benjamin Aaron (6/69-9/71), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Mr. Hildebrand-Correspondence (Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (B), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Mr. Hildebrand - Correspondence (Misc.)_ June 1969 - Sept. 1971, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Dr. Dale R. Corson (Cornell University), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (D), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (E), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (F), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (G), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence Prof. Walter Galenson June 1969 - Sept. 1971, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Personal - Prof. Gottfried Haberler, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Mr. Hildebrand -- Robt. J. Hines Correspondence and Thesis Draft, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Personal - Prof. Wayne L. Hodges (Cornell), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Mr. Hildebrand-Corresp. Paul Thomas Homan (6/69-9/71), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence Dean Alfred E. Kahn June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (J), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (L), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence Dr. T. C. LIU June 1969 - Sept. 1971, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Mr. Hildebrand-Corres. Dennis E. Mueller (6/69-9/71), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (N), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence Frank E. Norton June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (J), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (O), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (P and Q), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 ( R), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (J), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Mr. Hildebrand- Corresp. (6/69-9/71) Francis Marion Smith, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (T), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (U and V), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (W), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence John P. Windmuller (6/69-9/71), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Mr. Hildebrand Correspondence(Misc.) June 1969 - Sept. 1971 (X, Y, Z), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Souvenir - Photographs, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Speech - A. S. P. A. conference, Cornell Univ., 9/17/69, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Speech - National Foreign Trade Council, NYC - 9/24/69, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Speech - IBM Manager, Mt. Pocono, Pennsylvania (Oct. 22-23, 1969) (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Speech - UCLA, Los Angeles October 17, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Speech - Toronto-Hamilton Chapter of IRRA (12/2/70), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Speeches - Assn. of the Bar of the City of N.Y. 10/26/70, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Georgetown University - AIFLD Graduation Ceremonies (9/29/70), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Speech, Cornell Club of Maryland Sept.30, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Speeches - Seminar on "Foreign Investments 3/16/71, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Cords DMAC Progress Report, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Marx, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- The Problem of Unemployment, 1973-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Unemployment - Dual L.M. Theory, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- ILR 343 IEC. 342 - Problems in Labor Econ 1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Multi-National Firms, 1963-1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Income Distribution in theory and in fact, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Economics of Categorical Discrimination (Box 6, Folder 7)
- The Question of Technological Change (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Technological Change (Box 6, Folder 9)
- The Labor Movement and Industrialism: the American case (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Econ. 641 - Cumulative Notes (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Eco. 641 - ILR 648 - Seminar in Labor Economics, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Economics 442 - Economics and Problems of Labor of Labor - Spring 1967 - Room 117 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Some Current aspects of Collective bargaining in the United States, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- ILR-Eco 442 - Economics and Problems of Labor Fall 1967 - MWF 11:15 - Rm. 213 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- ILR 241-D - Rm 117 - MWF 2:30 Spring 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- The Problem of Poverty, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Econ. 411 - Scope and Method, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Econ. 411 - Demand Theory (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Labor Economics - Bibliographies, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 14.65 Labor Problems, 1953-1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Misc. (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Wage Theory - Historical, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Corporation Finance, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Molony "The Union need to Coordinate Bargaining", 1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- ILR 602 B - Arbitration, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Technological Change, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Work Rules and Working Conditions (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Collective Bargaining - Bibliographies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Arbitration - Introductory Observations, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Arbitration - Problems of Proof, Rules of Evidence (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Labor Economics - Bibliographies, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Arbitration + CB (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Eco. 825 - spring 1962 Trade Fluctuations (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Labor Economics -- Lecturers, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- ILR 540 -- Labor Market Economics, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- ILR 540, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- C.H. Stuart Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical + Atomic Workers, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Philips Dodge, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Bucyrus - Erie, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- P-D Ajo., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Eastern Container, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Phelps Dodge - Mar. 18, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Disval - USA - Mar. 13, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Carhart Photo - Local 317 Teamsters, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- E. Irondequoit Teachers Assoc., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Belmont Teachers Assoc. vs. Belmont Central School Dist., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Rome Central School -- Case # 15 39 0240 76, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- American Can - August, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Vacuum Chemicals Local 8-209 OCAW, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Hooker Chemicals + Plastics, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- PERB. City of Rome AFSCME, Council 6, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Niagara County Community College, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. Vs. IBEW Local 79, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Phelps Dodge Mar. 1, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Phelps Dodge (Tyrone) vs. USA Local 310 July 14, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Kennecott, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Bucyrus - Erie - Jan. 10. 1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Correspondence, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Phelps Dodge--Morenci vs USW, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Phelps Dodge Correspondence, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Phelps-Dodge - Bisbee, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Phelps Dodge -- El Paso vs USA Dist. 37, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Philps Dodge (New Cornelia) vs. Local 310 IBT, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Bencomo- Originally vs. PD, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Morenci, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Phelps Dodge (Morenci) vs. IAM, Lodge 1132 (Clarence Peete), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Phelps Dodge vs. USW of America - Local 310, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Phelps Dodge - D.L. Horne, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- P.D. vs. USSW, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- P.D. USA - Local 616, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Duwal Serrieta Corp./ U.S. Steelworkers Local 196, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- La Porte Plastics Corp. vs. USA Local 14997, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- UAW Local 787 - Lycoming Div., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Phelps Dodge - Douglas, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Phelps Dodge (Morenci) UB Carpenters + Jorners, Local No. 221, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Gold Bond vs. Oil, Chemical + Atomic Workers, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- N.Y. Air Brake vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Mach. Etc., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Armstrong Cork vs. Local 701 TWUA, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Hotel + Rest. 'ees vs. United Ford Mgmt. Services, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- USA Local H276 vs. GTE Sylvania Inc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- National - Standard, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Stauffer Chem Co. vs. OCAW, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Strong Memorial Hospital, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- P-D vs. USSN - El paso, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- United Paperworkers - International Local 1154 vs. Newton Falls Paper Mill, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Morse Chain vs. IAMAW Cayuga Lodge 1607 - Jan. 30, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- HEW vs. AFGE Local 3342 Jan. 26, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Driffy Mott vs. Local 220, RWDSU, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- IMAW Local 417, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Inspiration Consolidated Copper Co. v. IAM Lodge 933, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- USA vs. Evans Chemetics, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- American Optical Corp. vs. UGCW Local 222, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Ferro Corp. vs. USMA Local 2266, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Nestle Co. vs. Local 1974, RWDSU, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Pipe Welding Supply, Inc. Teamsters Local 529, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- USWA 12896 vs. Great Lakes, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Kennecott, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Syracuse China, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Inspiration Copper, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Portec Inc. vs. USWA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Phelps Dodge -- Ajo, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Phelps Dodge - Tyrone, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- CWA vs. Southwestern Bell Telephone Co., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Lederle Lub. Vs. Intern. Chem Workers, Local 143, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Phelps Dodge vs. USA Tyrone, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Dresser Transportation Equip vs. USA Local 1630 - May 12, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Graphite vs. Bricklayers, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Carborendum Co. vs. OCAW Local 8-12058, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Carrols Development vs. Local 317, Teamsters, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Inspiration Analysis, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Braswell Shipyards vs. Local 25, IUMSWA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Between Inspiration Consolidated Copper Company, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Report's Transcript of Proceedings, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Reporters' Transcript of Proceedings Volume 4, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Reporters' Transcript of Proceedings Volume 3, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Reporters' Transcript of Proceedings, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Misc., 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Misc., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Duval Sierrita Corporation, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Holden Educ. Assoc. vs. Holden School Comm., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Mobil Oil Corp. vs. OCAWIU Local 8-6220, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Rockwell International vs. USA Local 8173, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Duval - Aug. 19, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Kennedy Values vs. IAMAW Lodge 1379, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- AFSCMF Dist. Council 85 vs. Warren Co. Communications, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Glenn Electric Heater Corp. vs. IBEW Local 30, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Phelps Dodge -Tyrone- Jan. 17, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Vacuum - April 21, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Lipe Rollway vs. USWA Local 14929, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Southwestern Bell, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Pavilion Faculty vs. Pavilion Central School District, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Sterling Drug vs. ICWU Local 61 - Nov. 9, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Sears Bottle Blowers Assoc. vs. Foster-Forbes Glass Co., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Eber Bros vs. Teamsters Local 118, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Kennecott - Sept. 15, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- A.L. Lee Memorial Hospital vs. Local 200 SEIU, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- HEW vs. AFGE (Utica), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Lackawanna School Dist. Vs. Lackawanna Teachers Assoc. (NYSUT), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- NYS Nurse Assoc. Moses Ludington Hospital, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Sweet Home Education Assoc. vs. Sweet Home Central School District, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Federal Trade Commission (Box 11, Folder 22)
- PERB - City of Rochester + AFSCME, Local 1635, AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Attica Faculty Assoc. vs. Attica Central School Dist., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Watervfeit General, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Union Carbide Corp. vs. Local 8-250 OCAW, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Prospect Garden Convalescent vs. Local 1199, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Magma, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Magma Copper Nov. 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Capitol Foundry, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Dresser vs. Local 1630 USA, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Sheet Metal Workers vs. Animostat Products Div., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Fulton Consolidated Schools, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- GAF Corp., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Homestake Mining Company, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Hooker Chemical vs. NHEU, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Local 1630, USA vs. Dresser Ind., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- City of Olean, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Airco Speer Carbon-Graphite vs. Local 8 OCAWIU, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Interpace Corp. vs. Local 22485, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Nestle, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Ohio Power vs. Ohio Utility Workers, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Pittsburgh Press Company, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- USW, Local 890 vs. UV Industries, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Schenectady City Schools and Fed. Of Teachers Local 803, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Ritter Equip. Co. vs. Dist. Lodge 6, IAMAW, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- TWA - Aug. 12, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- TRW, Inc. vs. Local 338, UAW, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- UV Industries vs. USW, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Lipe Rollway Corp. vs. USA Local 14920, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Lipe Rollway vs. USA Loc 14929, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Kennedy Value Mfg. Co. vs. IAMAW Lodge 1379, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Spaulding Fibre Company, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Canisteo Central School, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Commonwealth vs. Alliance PS30-1977, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Phelps Dodge Refining Corp (El Paso) vs. USWA Local 501, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Phelps Dodge - Morenci, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Watervliet Arsenal vs. NAGE - Local R2-98, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. vs. IAMAW, Local 1790, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- J.F. McElivain Co. vs. N.H. Shoe Workers Union, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Schenectady Gazette vs. Typographical Union 167, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Tonawanda Coke Corporation, 1972-1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Hollingsworth + Vocal vs. Local 649 UPW, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- American Optical Corp. vs. United Glass + Ceramic Workers, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Phelps Dodge vs. United Transportation Union, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Columbian Rape, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Continental Airlines, Inc. vs. Local Union of Flight Attendants, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- U.A.W. of America vs. USA, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Seneca Falls Central School Dist. Vs. Seneca Falls Teachers Assoc., 1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Westinghouse Electric, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- East Irondequoit Central School Dist. Vs. NYSUT, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Olean Teachers vs. Olean Bd. Educ., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Olean Teachers; Association vs. Olean Board of Education, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Olean Teachers' Association vs. Olean Board of Education, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Kennecott Copper Corp., Utah Copper Division, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Lycoming Division of AVCO., 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Lycoming Division of AVCO, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Magma Copper Company, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Magma Copper Company, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Magma Copper Company, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Magma Copper Company, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Arbitration 21-77-22 thru 21-77-27, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts - Division of Employee Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Board of Conciliation and Arbitration Fact Finding, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Board of Conciliation and Arbitration Fact Finding, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Alliance, AFSCME/SEIU, AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Kennecott Copper Corp., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Alliance/AFSCME/SEIU, AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- USSW vs. Rockwell International Grievance No. 614, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Griffiss Air Force Base, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Capital Cities Broadcasting, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Ithaca College, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- United Paperworkers vs. American Can, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- American Can, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- United Paperworkers International vs. American Can, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Bristol School Comm. Vs. Bristol Educ. Assoc., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)